(Love Is Blooming)
Nice to see you all.
- All right. - After last week's preview...
(The sneak peek of Moo chewy cookies was in limelight.)
the comments...
(Chuckling)
They were waiting for this moment.
I'm not sure if it's a positive thing,
- but it did get a lot of attention. - Yes.
I wonder how Dubai chewy cookies feel about this, though.
They know their days are numbered.
(Muffled laughter)
Is this like a rain-calling ceremony to put an end to this trend?
No. I didn't want to put an end to it.
I wanted to popularize them.
Everyone jokingly said that I was going to end the trend.
But some people reacted differently.
"I'll finally get to have some now."
- Right. - Yes.
- There are always lines. - Right, there are always lines.
They were incredibly hard to come by.
- Right. - Yes.
I want to be able to buy them without having to line up.
So many people I know want to, but they can't because of the lines.
You wanted to unburden the distribution of the cookies.
You tried to stabilize the situation.
I wanted to normalize the distribution status.
So I was deployed on this.
He must be very influential.
It wasn't what I wanted, but I ended up becoming...
Trend Ending Man, not TSM.
Let's take a look.
- TSM. - Trend Ending Man.
- The Death of Trends. - Cutter of Trends.
"Chewy, Sweet, and Nutty."
(Chewy, Sweet, and Nutty, It's Endless)
(Groaning)
(Flicking)
My gosh.
- His pajamas remind me... - His pajamas...
The color looks off.
Of Bunta Takakura's pajamas in "Crayon Shin-chan."
(Half asleep, he walks over to the door.)
(Opening)
(He's opening the door when he just woke up.)
You're going out in those pajamas?
I don't have dementia.
Yes.
- What's that? - What is it?
Is that wine? What is it?
Are they ingredients for DCC?
They look quite fancy.
(Yawning)
(Current time, 7:20am)
I woke up too early.
(He's still sleepy, but he quickly opens up the package.)
It's packaged nicely.
Isn't that green onion?
Scallion. Why do you have that?
They look like tulips.
(Puzzled)
- They look too green. - So I have to add these?
- Bam. - Bam.
(Bam)
Mr. Deep in the Night,
Kyung Rok, left an impression on me.
So I started to buy flowers.
(Moomoo and Kyung Rok were born in the Year of the Snake, 1977.)
(They recently met on the show.)
(He's as energetic as a man born in the Year of the Snake.)
What a cute guy.
- He looked really happy. - Right.
So I wanted to try it too.
I recently found out that there was a flower delivery subscription.
Watching his clips really motivated me.
I signed up to the subscription the day after meeting him.
- Why do you keep trying to buy... - Listen.
Other people's lifestyles?
Right.
How many subscriptions do you hold now?
- I should have about six. - You get your produce delivered.
I started to order imperfect produce after watching Ja Yeon's clips.
The plants covering my wall are from my subscription service.
- That's a subscription too? - It is.
I bought flowers after watching Kyung Rok's clips.
- They're all subscription services? - Yes.
- He joined us only for one episode. - Yes.
You stole two things from him, Moomoo Day and flowers.
It went from Kyung Rok Day to Moomoo Day.
I'll go to Jebi Coffee House in the near future.
(Don't let your guard down, Kyung Rok.)
He's scary. He's stealing everything.
(He's stealing everything.)
(Just like Kyung Rok, )
(he calmly starts his day by filling the vase.)
(Gingerly placing the fresh flowers in the vase)
- I bought the vase too. - They're not in full bloom.
(Slightly under-bloomed tulips)
They'd look beautiful in a soju bottle.
(An honest comment of an expert florist)
(Look at that!)
(Snapping)
Plant Murderer.
(Let me see.)
Why do they look like green onions?
They sent under-bloomed tulips, though.
- I thought they were green onions. - Right. They're so...
- That way, they can last longer. - Right.
But why did you buy tulips out of all flowers?
- There are many flowers. - I like tulips.
- Why? - The color...
- They look the prettiest... - They come in many colors.
And have various colors.
Once they bloom, their petals...
- open up like this. - Right.
They're beautiful at every stage.
- Even their buds are beautiful. - They look like fruits.
Does this mean you're ending the tulip's popularity too?
This will even affect the Netherlands.
(It could gain international traction.)
- Even abroad? - It will have a major impact.
(Impressed)
Hiddink will be surprised.
(Moomoo's influence is on a global scale now.)
(He quickly opens up the next box of flowers.)
(Inhaling sharply)
Will they grow taller?
They look exactly the same. And they're the same color.
- What's that? - They're the same ones.
(They're the green-onion-looking tulips again.)
(Tilting his head)
They do look like green onions.
Right. They're very aromatic.
These ones will look different, right?
(Opening up the third box of flowers with hope)
They all look the same. Darn it.
- The petals are all closed. - Yes.
I ordered them in different colors, but they look all the same.
Right.
I remember ordering them in different colors.
They just look like scallions.
They're scallions.
(A new trend, green onion delivery subscription)
It felt like I just bought three bunches of scallions.
I bet they will taste great if we make fresh kimchi with them.
(I bet they will taste great if we make fresh kimchi with them.)
- Make fresh kimchi with them? - Make fresh kimchi with them.
(Make fresh tulip kimchi)
- It's tasty with ramyeon too. - Yes.
Totally.
(Careful)
(Placing the fresh green onion with utmost care)
- But once they bloom... - They look beautiful.
They will bloom beautifully, right?
(Scratching)
(He may be different from his friend, Kyung Rok, but...)
Kyung Rok has a prettier vase.
- Here's why, Hyun Moo. - Okay.
- You bought those vases together. - Right.
- But he bought them separately... - Right.
For different reasons and stories.
I didn't have time.
- It's like I'm on the run. - You were in a hurry.
I had to catch up like I was being chased.
You should have bought the vases on a subscription basis.
- Is there such a service? - They'll come inside?
You must change the water every day.
That way, you can delay them from withering away.
Sign up to a water-changing subscription.
I'll have 50 visitors a day then.
(A popular spot)
(Placing the soon-to-bloom tulips around his house)
(Trudging along)
(He quietly pulls out the exercise machine.)
- I exercise every morning. - The indoor bicycle.
- You should exercise. - You use the machine regularly.
- It's my morning routine. - Okay.
(Let me see.)
(Choose your workout.)
(Get ready.)
(He starts pedaling with ease.)
(Just like my friend Kyung Rok...)
I should start my day with a good sweat.
I can engage my core muscles since there's no handle.
(Let's get this workout started.)
I'll just do it for ten minutes. Let's go.
- I used it so much that... - You should wake up.
I ended up replacing the seat.
- Really? - I rode it so much.
- You didn't buy a new one. - I'm almost there.
But you only replaced the seat.
(Laughing)
Stop.
(Finally!)
(Panting)
It's nice that I can record my workouts.
- Ten minutes. - I do it for at least ten minutes.
- Look at you sweating. - I'm sweating so much.
(He's sweating profusely.)
- I got sweaty just in ten minutes. - Gosh, I'm hot.
(He perfectly completes his morning routine.)
(Washing his hands thoroughly with cool water)
(Rolling up his sleeves)
(I don't have time to rest.)
(Uncovering)
I got a lot done yesterday.
What's that?
(He's tired, but he uncovers something.)
- What's that? - What?
I did that for two hours last night before going to sleep.
- Are they pistachios? - What is that?
- Are they peanuts? What are those? - Pistachios.
- What are those? - Pistachios.
As you all wished, I will finally make...
Moo chewy cookies.
Watch your six, Dubai chewy cookies.
(Moo chewy cookies)
Dubai chewy cookies,
also known as DCC, are gaining a lot of popularity.
(The whole country is crazy for DCC.)
Right.
(It's chewy on the outside and crispy on the inside.)
(Due to its addictive flavor, its popularity shows...)
(no signs of slowing down.)
(Bum June visited Yoo Ji Tae with precious Dubai chewy cookies.)
(Envious)
Things were great back then.
Things were great back then?
(TSM Hyun Moo received endless requests from DCC lovers.)
(When will you make Dubai chewy cookies?)
(Let's put an end to this trend.)
(Dubai chewy cookies think they're all that.)
(They're super snobby.)
(Dubai chewy cookies' popularity is skyrocketing.)
They're always sold out.
You always have to wait for them for 1 or 2 hours.
- Right. - That leaves me with no choice.
I should make my own Dubai chewy cookies.
I decided to make them because I wanted them.
Remember leng saeb?
Oh, leng saeb.
(He cooked it while making a scene.)
I had to cook my own leng saeb because I couldn't find it.
To make authentic Dubai chewy cookies,
I'm going to start from scratch.
To make Dubai chewy cookies, I have to start...
by roasting pistachios and blending them.
That painting is getting on my nerves.
(Laughing)
It's annoying, right?
Then the wrapper is made with marshmallows and butter.
I must melt them on low heat.
Once they melt, I add cocoa powder and dried whole milk...
to get that chocolatey color. That's how you make the wrapper.
Afterward, you wrap the filling up with it.
Then Dubai chewy cookies are ready.
Anyway, I'm putting my reputation on the line for this.
When my reputation is at stake, I always do a painting about it.
You see,
I'm the magician of colors.
It wasn't hard to paint this.
I can see that.
Don't cheap Dubai chewy cookies have that color?
- Fake ones. - Right?
Ta-da.
You can't execute this kind of color...
by following science or calculating math.
I was in my moment.
- "Ta-da." - Look at his hand movements.
I don't know how I ended up with this color.
It's all in my instincts.
It's not something that can be taught.
(It's me, Moo chewy cookies.)
(Shutting his eyes)
I still have his first painting.
The value of that painting must be crazy.
I can no longer paint with that style.
- No, right? - No.
- Your style has become too simple. - Right.
- Right, it's simple. - Back then, you used many colors.
For CODE KUNST's portrait painting, I took my time with it.
Also, I took breaks.
But now, it seems I paint for commercial purposes.
Commercial purposes.
- I have no time, so it got simple. - You don't have time.
Your style became simple.
You know what? Your art is falling into a pattern too.
- And his current paintings... - That's more annoying.
- are symmetrical these days. - Right.
- When he started, they weren't. - Yes.
- They became repetitive. - That kind of thing happens...
- after 20 years of painting. - I mean,
- he's trying to be professional. - I didn't have time back then.
His works became repetitive after drawing a few paintings.
I must break out of my patterns.
(He's diligently opening pistachios for Moo chewy cookies.)
Let's make them the authentic way.
Opening them is the first step of Dubai chewy cookies.
I came home after work last night and then opened half of them.
You did that yourself?
They didn't sell shelled ones.
So you had to open them yourself? All by hand?
It took me two weeks to get them.
- There are shelled ones. - Because there are no pistachios?
- Right. - But it's impossible to buy them.
Actually, I wanted to make them too.
So I asked my sister for some pistachios.
- She couldn't find them... - She couldn't find them either?
- even for her bakery. - No pistachios?
It's hard to get other ingredients that go into these cookies...
like cocoa powder...
- and white chocolate. - Right.
So she couldn't make other products.
But you couldn't find that thing?
- What? - The green jam or something.
- The spread? - The spread.
That's not the authentic way.
- I'm going legit with this. - Right.
- But it's way tastier that way. - It's good.
- You're making it from scratch. - Exactly.
I still have so many to open. When will I finish?
(Oh, no.)
That's a lot of pistachios.
- So 1 bag weighs about 1.36kg. - My gosh.
Just one bag?
Opening them is really tough on your hands.
This part hurt like crazy.
(He focuses on cracking them open while bearing the pain.)
There are always stubborn ones.
(Wincing)
You look cute like a chipmunk.
You keep cracking them open.
He's mocking Hyun Moo.
(Laughing)
You look like an old squirrel.
- Get rid of "old." - I see them a lot in Gwacheon.
- Right. - Oh, those clumsy ones?
- Yes. - Those squirrels with dry fur.
(Chip-Moo keeps shelling the pistachios.)
You're saying lovely things about me.
(Chip-Moo is working hard to make authentic DCC.)
(Crackling)
You look so lonely because you're doing it alone.
(Looking over)
(He stops shelling and gets up.)
(He takes out an LP record to break the silence.)
Seriously.
- Seriously. - I was inspired by Kyung Rok.
(Listening to the record just like his friend, Kyung Rok)
It was too lonely and quiet.
Playing music is good.
(The music resonates throughout the quiet house.)
(He starts shelling pistachios again...)
(as classical music fills the silence.)
(The table is getting messier.)
(And the record player is spinning.)
(And there seems to be no end to the world of pistachios.)
(Moomoo reaches the stage where he begins to enjoy the work.)
That must've been a lot of work.
Once you keep shelling them, you stop thinking.
- Right. - You start spacing out.
- People space out. - They space out.
(There are still a lot of pistachios left.)
You should do that kind of work in the morning.
- Strangely, you get lazy at night. - Right.
That's so true.
(For authentic Dubai chewy cookies...)
I look like a master.
(Pistachio shells begin to pile up.)
Your house looks quite fancy with the flowers.
- Right? - Yes.
Don't I look like a grandpa from the Netherlands?
(The grandpa from the Netherlands is hooked on pistachios.)
He's calling himself old.
(Blasting)
"Ba-dum."
I'm done!
(I'm done too!)
(This should be enough.)
(He finally escapes from the pistachio abyss.)
(He checks the recipe before he starts making them.)
I need 640g of pistachios.
- The recipe is that long? - Of course.
A lot of effort goes into making them.
- They're expensive for a reason. - There's a reason for it.
Making them requires a lot of work.
Where did you get the recipe?
I looked up a lot of recipes.
I chose the recipe that used raw ingredients from scratch.
Not the recipe with pistachio spread...
or kadayif.
There was a recipe with only raw ingredients.
I chose that one.
(The recipe from scratch)
I need 640g.
(He starts by weighing the shelled pistachios.)
You need 640g? Isn't that a lot?
A lot of people wanted it, so I'll give them out as presents.
I see. As presents.
I thought about making 20 to 30 cookies.
(The recipe yields about 30 cookies.)
(Pouring)
What? Did I shell too many?
The maximum weight is 1,000g.
I had a lot of leftover pistachios.
(It went over the maximum weight, 1,000g.)
(Leaving only the amount of pistachios he needs)
That's 640g.
You should've used them all. Why did you leave some?
I needed to follow the recipe.
I didn't want the flavor to change.
That's what I heard. When it comes to baking,
- you must measure precisely. - Right.
- Even 1g can change the flavors. - You need to be precise.
(The difference of 1g could change the outcome in baking.)
"Roast them in the preheated oven for 5 to 7 minutes."
(Roast 640g of pistachios at 150°C for 5 to 7 minutes.)
My gosh, seriously. This is a great oven.
(Opening)
That's my oven.
You said you'd take it later.
- Right. He said that. - I asked him to store it for me...
until I made some space for it.
- That's Venix, right? - That's right. How did you know?
My sister uses an oven from Unox.
- That's a higher grade. - Right.
That's why I was eyeing that oven too.
Then he bought it from you.
- That's a great oven. - Right.
(You know its value.)
Before I give it to Jae Hyeon,
I should make sure it's working.
Right.
I'm going to give him everything. They all cost money to buy.
It's all money.
(Pouring out the shelled pistachios)
I should have preheated the oven.
(Oh, right!)
(The pistachios are on standby for now.)
(Turning on the oven)
(The current temperature is at 22°C.)
The oven should be preheated at 150°C.
Roast them to 5 to 7 minutes.
It doesn't take long for the oven to heat up.
Right.
(Heat up fast.)
- My gosh. - What happened?
Please. No!
(It's a disaster.)
I hate it! What's he going to do?
I'm stressed.
(Chuckling)
(Thud)
(Pain-causing cookies)
"Pain-causing cookies."
My gosh. Come on.
(Plopping down)
Oh, dear. Come on.
(It's a huge mess.)
When your anger is on another level,
- you don't even feel angry. - Totally. I know what you mean.
- I'd be so speechless. - I bet you wanted to crush them.
- "Darn it. I won't do it." - I had no energy to curse even.
(He even loses the will to get angry.)
- You can't even laugh about it. - I was so annoyed.
You have a long way to go.
(There's a long way ahead of me.)
Darn it. I can't use them since they're so dirty.
(Covered in dust)
I should shell some more. Darn it.
There goes my entire morning!
(Feeling dejected)
Darn it.
I just hated myself.
I didn't even get angry because I felt so pathetic.
I didn't even want to talk...
to myself.
Here's why. When I was placing the tray down,
I noticed that it was slightly slanted.
It was slightly slanted.
- Right. - My gosh.
- That looks unstable. - I didn't think it would fall.
- Right. - That looks so unstable.
I was so dispirited.
(An overlooked moment led to disaster.)
This is so stressful.
The chipmunk is in despair.
(Chip Moo is in a state of dejection.)
(I should clean them up quickly.)
My gosh. Darn it.
- He can't even blame other people. - Right.
- He caused it. - Right.
(The more he thinks about it, the angrier he gets.)
Darn it.
(Crunchy)
I should eat them.
Darn it.
(Scowling)
I bet his entire house is covered in pistachios.
My house smelled nutty.
(Sighing)
(Grabbing)
(Laughing)
He's annoyed.
Stop falling off the tray. Please.
(Pleading)
(Falling out)
(Sighing)
(Measuring the pistachios he put aside earlier)
(Without the bowl, they weigh 395g.)
(Tapping)
I need to shell 245g more.
- You need to shell a little more. - A little more. Just 245g more.
(He needs 245g more due to the mistake.)
I would've used them...
- if they were for me. - Right.
- But they were for other people. - They were presents for others.
- That's iffy. - Seriously.
You could have rinsed them in water and roasted them.
- Really? You should've told me. - Yes.
- Just wipe them... - He didn't know this happened.
(He didn't know. How could he?)
(Watching)
It's increasing by 1g.
Per pistachio?
- Come on. - Oh, no.
(Each pistachio weighs 1g without the shell.)
I still have to shell a lot more.
(It turned out 640g of pistachios meant shelling 640.)
You have to be that precise about the weight?
It was my first time. I wanted to follow the recipe exactly.
It's increasing slowly like the calories I burn.
- Right. That's a good analogy. - I can relate to that.
It will take forever to shell them.
(It's already been 50 minutes since he started.)
(Step 1: Shell pistachios.)
(He's still on the 1st step.)
You haven't gotten past the first step.
Gosh, seriously.
Why did I eat that?
(I don't want to waste it.)
Gosh, this is a lot.
They're expensive for a reason.
They're expensive for a reason. It requires so much work.
It really does.
I'm almost there.
Okay. One more gram.
(Dropping)
There you go!
- I got it. - He finished.
(He escapes from the pistachio abyss after much effort.)
Good.
I shelled enough for 60 servings.
I ate about 200 pistachios.
So I shelled about 1,200 pistachios.
I shelled more pistachios than a regular chipmunk.
(Hang in there, Old Chip-Moo.)
(The pistachios are finally entering the oven.)
Roast the oven for 5 to 7 minutes.
(He finally activates the oven.)
(Is it going well?)
(Golden brown)
(Amazed)
It smells so nutty. Oh, my.
Take them out carefully. Don't drop them.
(Smelling)
It smells so nutty. This is no joke.
They smell different, right?
- Definitely. They're much nuttier. - Does the smell get stronger?
You're putting them up there again?
Oh, no. I'm getting nervous. Why are you doing that?
Why do you keep putting them there?
(Why on earth?)
- No! - No. Why are you doing that?
Fine. Let them fall again.
(Realizing his mistake)
(Relieved)
- I almost put it there. - This is hot.
I must have lost my mind.
It's so hot.
It's hot.
(The pistachios are safely delivered.)
(Relieved)
(Cool them for some now.)
He hasn't even started on making the spread. Oh, no.
I basically got nothing done.
(Rummaging through)
(He grabs something and comes to the kitchen.)
That's done. All right.
I need 600g of soft flour.
I didn't know flour went into it.
(He's adding soft flour after working on the pistachios?)
Okay.
I need 300g...
- of corn starch. - That's 300g of corn starch.
Write that down.
So 600g and 300g.
Next, I have to sift them?
I did the same thing before,
- and my sister scolded me a lot. - Darn it.
(He's asking to get scolded for the flour mess.)
Oh, no. His phone.
(His phone falls victim.)
When everyone watches this,
the trend of DCC will be over.
I didn't mean anything by it.
- It's so annoying to watch. - Exactly.
Out of all the recent videos I watched, this is...
- the most annoying one. - It's so stressful.
Watching him make the cookies should be fun and enjoyable.
But why is his video making me so angry?
- So it's a complicated recipe. - Right.
(Making Moo chewy cookies is harder than one might think.)
(But he's still trying his best.)
(The flour is getting sifted finely thanks to his hard work.)
I need 12g of white vinegar.
White vinegar?
I need 168g of canola oil.
How fascinating.
Then add cold water to them.
"Stir well until it becomes watery."
Then sift it again?
Why isn't it turning liquid?
Why is this... My gosh. Did it solidify?
Out of everything I did today, I put the most care...
into making kadayif.
I'm making kadayif now.
(The key ingredient of DCC, kadayif)
- It's Middle Eastern noodles. - Now, I get it.
They're so popular that...
- it's impossible to buy them now. - Right.
So I decided to make them.
- You didn't use substitutes? - You decided to make them instead.
- I didn't. - I see.
- That's Moo-dayif. - Right.
You made your own kadayif.
Making the noodles will take a lot of time.
(He starts making kadayif.)
This is the thickness I need.
It's watery. Nice.
I think it will work.
- It has to be watery? - Yes.
- Right. - It must go into the piping bags.
(He's sifting the batter one more time.)
After watching this clip, I can now understand why...
- Right. - they're so expensive.
"Sift it and put it into a piping bag."
"Make a hole with a needle."
"Squeeze out very thin noodles on the pan..."
- Right. - "and cook them."
That's crazy.
Only a needle should be able to pass through.
If it's too big, they become kalguksu noodles.
Then it's over.
(Staring)
It should be really tiny.
(It can't get too big.)
You can't mess up this part.
Oh, my. You need to be delicate.
(Careful)
Hold tightly.
(Make very thin noodles.)
- This is how you do it? - Like that?
- That's how you do it? - What?
I'm making kadayif now.
You're making them individually?
- Of course. - It will take forever then.
Do you know the sauce bottle for takoyaki?
I saw bakers use the bottle to make kadayif.
- Right. - Yes.
(He's doing it the hard way when it can be much easier.)
Come on. Darn it.
(Squeezing out diligently)
(Utterly focused)
I'll stop here for now.
- They look so different. - Oh, no.
- It looks like mayonnaise. - They're thick.
- The hole was quite big. - Was it?
- They should've been thinner. - Right.
- They should be as thin as needles. - They have to be super thin.
What?
(Scraping)
(They're coming off, though.)
(Chuckling)
He's cute.
It's working.
- I get it now. - He gets it now.
- He's getting the hang of it now. - My gosh.
(He gives squeezing out the batter another try.)
- You got it. - You're good.
(The batter is coming out quite thinly now.)
To make them crispy,
I preheated the oven at 150°C...
and roasted them for 5 to 7 minutes.
On top of that, I removed all the moisture...
and fried them with butter.
You have to fry them with butter.
This looks pretty legit.
I was able to crisp them up.
(He finally makes crispy and crunchy kadayif.)
Pistachio and chocolate.
(Next, he will make the filling.)
Seriously. Making them requires a lot of work.
Here it goes. I'll make the spread next.
I need 60g of canola oil.
Okay.
It's 61g.
Gosh, he's in trouble.
I'll do half and half.
(Filling it up with pistachios)
I added too much.
I'll only add half too.
(Pouring the canola oil)
(He pours out the next ingredient without hesitation.)
I need 220g of white chocolate.
(I need to add 70g more.)
This is a lot of work.
You used chocolate from Valrhona.
- Is that a good brand? - Yes.
I'm glad he knows that.
Just have sweet cookies.
(Forget about measuring.)
(Adding 300g of chocolate to sweeten them up)
I stopped measuring them.
It was so annoying.
(He puts the chocolate in the microwave.)
It's fine. They'll just be sweet.
Half a pinch of salt.
(He follows his gut and adds more than half a pinch of salt.)
(Placing the bottle, completely full, into the blender)
- That startled me. - It will create some smoke.
- The motor almost exploded. - Right. I bet.
The color looks pretty legit.
It's turning green.
My gosh.
(Gosh, it worked.)
(After a boost of confidence...)
White chocolate.
The melted white chocolate from earlier.
(Adding a spoonful of white chocolate)
(Licking)
It's amazing.
(It looks similar to the store-bought pistachio spread.)
It's perfect.
(He takes out a new spoon.)
I wonder how it tastes.
- It's very savory. - Is it very rich?
(Impressed)
It's so tasty. It's just like spread.
It'll be delicious on bread.
It isn't too sweet. I love it.
(Impressed)
It's so thick.
(That's what I'm talking about.)
- It's thick and rich. - That's right. Rich.
This spread is really tasty.
(Mixing)
It's perfect.
(Kadayif and pistachio become one.)
I'll begin the dung beetle's work in earnest.
(I'll begin the dung beetle's work in earnest now.)
(He puts on his gloves properly.)
(Licking)
(Scooping)
- Experts call it... - Okay.
- the dung beetle's work. - The dung beetle's work?
The pieces are small.
(Moo Dung Beetle puts it down gently.)
What's wrong with it?
There's nothing wrong with it.
Why is it doing that?
- I like it moist. - Is that so?
I prefer the moist filling like that one.
I think that one should be called wet.
It'd be more appropriate to call it wet.
(Glancing over)
(It's pistachio filling, but...)
Everyone, it's pistachio.
Please don't misunderstand.
It looks so unappetizing. For goodness' sake.
(Oh, no)
I can't believe how unappetizing it looks.
(Moo Dung Beetle tries to salvage it...)
(with his artistic soul.)
(Fiddling)
Tanzania.
- Twelve. - What...
(The 12 blobs seem to show the changing process.)
What...
What... What's that in the right corner?
- There wasn't enough kadayif. - I see.
I ran out.
(Stretching)
(He uses a plastic bag to cover the precious Moo chewy cookies.)
(They go into the fridge.)
(Sighing)
My goodness.
- They were dirty dishes. - My goodness.
(A big mess)
It looks so bad.
It really looks like cow dung.
How did you clean it up?
Oh, no. He's spreading it.
(Wiping)
Gosh, this is...
Since the ingredients were oil and chocolate,
- it must've been hard to clean up. - That's right. The oil stains.
(Wiping)
(He wipes the traces from the nooks and crannies.)
It really looks like dung.
Gosh, it looks so bad.
Why doesn't it look as good as it tastes?
I briefly thought about throwing away the induction stove.
(I briefly thought about throwing away the induction stove.)
(My goodness)
The puffiness is gone, Hyun Moo.
- You know that I worked hard. - How did they come up with it?
Must you do everything manually?
- That's right. - Can't you use a machine?
Everything is done manually.
One peels pistachios, one kneads the dough,
and one bakes the kadayif. The tasks are divided up.
There's another person to score the ingredients.
- That's right. - That's right.
I shouldn't have looked down on the Dubai chewy cookies.
- They live up to their fame. - They live up to their fame.
It's time to make the wrapper.
(It's time to make the wrapper.)
Okay.
(The current time is 11am.)
This is 400g and I need 140g.
(This is 400g of butter.)
(Cutting)
You didn't measure the amount.
I stopped doing that at one point.
It's exactly 140g.
Okay.
I need 60g of cocoa powder.
(His goal is 60g of cocoa powder.)
Five grams. Five grams are fine.
It'll just get richer.
And 30g of dry milk.
(With 65g of cocoa powder and 30g of dry milk, )
(his goal is a total of 95g.)
All done.
Once the marshmallows melt, I'll add them.
(He picks up a bag of marshmallows.)
- What? - What? My goodness.
(He pours out the entire bag.)
Are you supposed to add that much?
(Without hesitation, he empties one more bag.)
It'll be so fattening.
I'll need to run around the globe about 15 times.
Like this.
Apparently, marshmallows are pretty low-calorie.
- That's right. - That's right.
- Marshmallows feel so victimized. - That's right.
But it's best not to eat them if you can help it.
Of course.
It's melting.
It's turning into marshmallow in Choco Pie.
Around this time...
(Let's see. Around this time...)
You add cocoa powder.
(Sprinkle the cocoa powder and dry milk.)
- That's how you melt it. - That's right.
(Mix well with the melted marshmallows.)
It's soft like my belly.
(He's carefree after making a mean comment.)
These punks look cute.
It took on one color.
- You did a good job. - Right? It looks nice.
All done.
(Fascinated)
Like this.
(The marshmallow wrapper gets cooled down for a moment.)
Now comes the final step.
There are two versions.
A must-have item for the Gen Zers, matcha.
Matcha.
I'll finish off matcha as well.
(His eyes are crazed.)
Cocoa powder and... Very nice.
- Do you roll them on the top? - You roll them.
- They take so much effort. - Seriously.
Are they cooled down?
(He checks up on the spread he cooled down earlier.)
Ta-da.
(Oh, my)
Good. They look perfect.
"They look perfect?"
(Grinning)
(Grabbing)
It hardened.
What do you do with that?
(He shapes the hardened spread.)
This is the dung beetle's work they talk about on YouTube.
(Rolling)
It smells so savory.
(Impressed)
- It must be delicious. - I must be a genius.
(Oh, my!)
I see...
that it can be done.
(He gains confidence and shapes the filling.)
- It's too big like a fat macaron. - It's big-sized.
- It should cost 40 dollars. - Did you say 40 dollars?
This one doesn't have the crunchy ingredient.
It's a dud.
If you eat it, it's a dud.
(Laughing)
There isn't much kadayif.
Why is it so small?
I couldn't adjust the size.
Couldn't you pull some out?
- Two duds. - I was too exhausted.
(He lacked the stamina.)
It's too big.
A Dubai chewy cookie of this size should cost 50 dollars.
All of them are shaped differently.
(He puts on new gloves when the spread is ready.)
He's very neat.
(Grabbing)
(He pours oil over the new gloves.)
Does it prevent sticking?
It prevents marshmallow from sticking.
(It's time to cover the filling with the marshmallow wrapper.)
It must be hard to wrap it.
- It looks like hotteok. - That's right.
Right?
- I bet it feels nice. - Yes, it feels nice.
(He adds the spread inside the broad wrapper.)
The wrapper is too thick.
Hold on.
- How will you... - What's that?
How will you eat it?
(My goodness)
That's my aesthetic goal.
I like Dubai chewy cookies that are excessive in every way.
The wrapper should be thick...
like a big dumpling.
It needs to be chewy.
As for kadayif, it should give the texture...
of munching on sand.
It should be crunchy enough to break the teeth.
That's the texture I want.
(He breaks free from the normal amount.)
It looks nice.
Okay.
(Moo chewy cookies aren't stingy with ingredients.)
Why... Hold on.
(Hold on. Is it too big?)
(He takes off some marshmallows.)
It's still big.
- I should use a bit at a time. - Is the tasty wrapper...
thick or thin?
These days, the thin wrapper is...
- Is it the trend? - Yes.
Let's make it smaller.
How about this much?
Thin.
(He spreads it out thinly to follow the current trend.)
It's the size we're familiar with.
I can use a small amount.
(He improves through trials and errors.)
As thin as the xiaolongbao wrapper.
Moo chewy cookies.
(Sinking)
Seriously.
Fat chewy cookie.
(He enjoys making Moo chewy cookies.)
Fat.
Thinly. One,
two, three.
(Ta-da!)
- He suddenly became excited. - It was exciting.
(The tactile play excites Child Moo.)
Okay.
Anger disappeared from his face.
This one is like potato rice cake.
It's big.
This one is like musubi. Mu chewy cookie.
This one is like a dumpling. Dump chewy cookie.
He's coming up with new words.
Two... There's no more. I'm in trouble.
I ran out.
- What? - What do you do then?
You should sacrifice yourself.
(He collects marshmallow from the ready-made ones.)
What should I do with this?
The filling is visible in this one.
This one is like an inside-out sushi roll.
This hasn't been attempted before.
- Oh, my. - My goodness.
Inside-out Dubai chewy cookie.
- My goodness. - Gosh.
(They can't help but groan.)
Gosh, that's...
- I can't believe it. - Gosh.
Cow dung cookie.
(What do you think?)
I'm beginning to shape them nicely instead of playing around.
I'll cover the burst areas with the powder.
They'll look fine once the burst areas are covered.
(He applies the cocoa and matcha powder evenly.)
Good.
- Don't they look nice? - I can see that they're handmade.
- Not bad. - You did well.
- My goodness. - My goodness.
(Store-bought Dubai chewy cookies versus Moo chewy cookies)
Did it take five hours?
- It's past 12pm. - Okay.
It's lunchtime.
Shall I package them now?
(He bought cases for Dubai chewy cookies.)
They won't fit since they're so big.
It's pretty.
What's this?
For goodness' sake.
- What? - Isn't it upside down?
- That's the bottom side. - I didn't know.
For goodness' sake.
(Is it a faulty product?)
It looks strange.
- It's a random box. - Yes.
- It's like a draw. - It keeps you excited.
(He continues to wrap them secretively.)
I won't be able to close it.
It's too big.
- I love how he broke the mold. - Yes.
What should I do?
The shape should be pretty.
Isn't this more hip?
It's hip.
It looks very valuable.
- Doesn't it look hip? - It looks like...
that dog thing on the street.
- Poop bag? - Poop bag.
Let's go.
(Dog poop cookie)
It's like a special treat.
It looks like a hard-to-get item.
Break free from the mold of packaging everything prettily.
- That's right. - That's what I'm talking about.
(Next step for the special treat)
It's a limited edition.
There are stickers. That's good.
Hyun Moo, that's good.
- That's incredible. - Don't they look nice?
Sticking them haphazardly makes them look hip.
(A packaging you might see at a hip cafe)
- It looks nice. - It looks nice, right?
They're from a store that's so popular...
that the owner doesn't care about nice packaging.
(Laughing)
(He finishes packaging the gifts.)
I want those stickers.
Let's try one and see how it tastes.
(Chewy)
It's chewy.
It's really chewy, right?
It's like a store-bought one.
It looks like you're eating a live octopus.
Seriously.
- Listen to that sound. - It's crunchy.
- Crunchy. - The filling is so thick.
- Rich and moist. - Not bad.
Rich and moist.
Chewy.
What is it?
Dubai chewy cookie lips.
(Dubai chewy cookie lips are popular among Gen Zers.)
(Don't even think about it.)
It's the same thing.
- Come here. - I'm so freaking angry.
Why are you angry?
(Gen Z Moomoo leaves a trendy shot as well!)
What's up with those eyes?
They're sexy.
Your eyes are annoying, not your mouth.
(He acts sexy with Moo chewy cookies on his lips.)
He paused for a second.
- Gosh. - He looks like a zombie.
Moo chewy cookies were a success.
(Happy)
I feel like I'm in Haeundae.
The floor feels sandy.
It's a mess.
(A mess)
- Oh, no. - I can feel them under my feet.
I'll clean up later.
(He puts off cleaning up and collapses on the sofa.)
Gosh, I'm dying. My goodness.
He must be totally drained.
- He spent five hours, right? - He's done for the day.
Dubai chewy cookies practically killed me.
- He collapsed. - Foot chewy cookies.
- Gosh. - Foot chewy cookies.
(With Moo chewy cookies all over his body, he falls asleep.)
(Blinking)
Gosh, I need to wash up. I feel icky.
(He washes up after creating a masterpiece.)
I feel so refreshed.
Even his outfit is the color of Dubai chewy cookies.
That's right. It's the color of pistachio.
Gosh, it'll finally leave me.
My goodness. I hope it'll fit in the vehicle.
After Dubai chewy cookies, it's a goodbye.
For the customers of the Grand Rainbow Bazaar,
I prepared Moomoo's After-Sales Service.
Moomoo's After-Sales Service.
I'll do anything to give you guys goosebumps.
(Peek-a-boo)
During the Grand Rainbow Bazaar...
(Familiar faces visited the Grand Rainbow Bazaar.)
Many people donated money for the good cause.
To express gratitude, I decided to give...
additional items...
- or upgraded items. - It's the after-sales service.
And some items haven't been delivered yet...
because of their big size.
(The huge oven caught everyone's attention.)
Jae Hyeon decided to take it.
(Jae Hyeon bought it in a cool manner.)
I need to deliver the item myself.
So I'll do the delivery and after-sales service...
and provide a free gift in addition.
- I'm so thankful. - I'll do everything.
(Groaning)
Gosh, it's huge.
How will you take it?
There's a wheeled cart underneath it.
(Heave-ho)
It's heavy.
(He moves the oven and the cart to the doorway.)
Dubai chewy cookies.
(He goes to the kitchen to fetch Moo chewy cookies.)
It's the after-sales service gift.
- For the customers? - For the customers.
They'll be moved when they watch this.
- It took five hours. - I really hope they watch it.
Five hours and a half.
Good.
(After packing the Moo chewy cookies, )
(it's 1:45pm.)
Let's go.
(He takes the oven...)
(and sets off for the after-sales service.)
Even the car is the color of Dubai chewy cookies.
He matched the color.
(On his way to provide after-sales service)
(I love you)
("I love you" is the only thing)
The song came out when I was studying for CSAT again.
(He goes somewhere with the chewy sentimentality.)
(Vocalizing)
- I'm nearly there. - Whose place is he going to?
Four minutes.
Sangsu.
There were so many places to visit.
It's the Jebi Coffee House
Let's herd the swallows
Is Kyung Rok there?
Did you go to meet Kyung Rok?
Who will it be?
(He arrives at the house of the first customer...)
This is the place.
(for the after-sales service.)
(He walks over with luggage.)
There's a red carpet on the floor.
(Summoning the customer)
- The bag burst. - The bag burst.
I guess it was too big.
What's this? The bag burst.
(Peeking)
(Dear customer, Moo chewy cookies are here.)
Is the house empty?
Oh, no.
Hello?
Hyun Moo, can you hear me?
Why aren't you opening the door?
The first house I visited for Moomoo's After-Sales Service...
belonged to Im Woo Il who bought the equestrian machine.
The item that weighed the most heavily in my heart...
was the equestrian machine.
(He rode the equestrian machine at the Grand Rainbow Bazaar.)
By using this, you can exercise more.
(Woo Il bought an equestrian machine with a broken pedal.)
One pedal was missing.
So I looked everywhere...
and found the fitting part.
- The pedal. - How did you find it?
The machine was from ten years ago.
- The company no longer makes it. - I'm not surprised.
- Did you look it up on Karrot? - I looked it up on Karrot...
and the internet.
It was a completely rare item.
I thought you were home right now. I'm in front of your house.
I just got done with work.
You should press the passcode and go up then.
You're going to tell me the passcode?
- Yes. - Go ahead.
It's...
How can you just say it like that?
(His passcode gets revealed to everyone.)
Are you serious?
Right.
Hurry up and change it.
But my unit wasn't revealed, so no one will know.
It's Unit...
How can you reveal that?
Use actual keys now.
Right.
There's even a partition door installed here.
Will there be something valuable to take away?
Probably not.
- There's the equestrian machine. - Right.
It's nice and cozy.
The view is great.
(He enjoys the Han River view without the owner of the house.)
The house doesn't smell bad.
(Sniffing)
I can see how he lives here.
He must lie around here.
(Looking around)
Oh, here it is!
(Oh, here it is!)
What?
This side was the problem.
(Coming apart)
(Rustling)
It's brand new.
The after-sales service is great.
(Shall I begin with the after-sales service?)
(He quickly removes the broken pedal.)
(Tapping)
(The new pedal is fixed to the equestrian machine.)
It must be touching to see it fixed when he comes back.
There we go!
It's fixed.
(The broken pedal has been repaired.)
It should be tested.
Right. It should be tested.
It's on now.
(Shall I give it a try?)
Gosh, it's perfect.
Full-body exercise.
(Impressed)
Gosh, it's great.
Giddy-up!
How is it now? Is it sturdy?
Check out my right foot.
- It's sturdy now. - Gosh.
Should I take this back? It's nice.
(The ride quality leaves the previous owner with regret.)
(Even the repair check is over.)
Great.
Let's get off carefully.
I can see how he lives.
He covers himself with this...
and lies down like this.
Gosh, this is the best.
It's great here.
His house was great.
I would stay there all day if I were him.
He takes in a lot of medicine.
Hangover cures and diet medicine.
I barely take them.
- He's here! - He's here!
- That startled him. - Hyun Moo.
(Rushing inside)
Hyun Moo.
Hyun Moo!
(Quiet)
(Hyun Moo doesn't answer back even after being called for.)
What?
It would be hilarious if he hides under his bed...
and lives there for a few days.
(Did he leave?)
It feels like a scene from a movie.
- What? - What?
(Did he leave his phone?)
(Opening)
- I got a call. - What? Come on!
(Startled)
- What was that? Are you serious? - Oh, you were the one to call.
You were just like a middle schooler.
- Not an elementary schooler. - Why didn't you check the room?
- What? - Your house is great.
I wanted to ask you about this. Why did you hide?
I just wanted to prank you.
I understand that heart, though.
- Same here. - You get it, right?
- He didn't do anything. - There was no purpose for it.
- He didn't even startle me. - Nothing.
I just wanted to stress you out.
- For a brief moment? - Right.
I do that when my mom comes.
I hide when I hear the beeping.
- It's an instinct. - Why do you do that?
I have no idea why.
- Everyone does that. - I do that with Anju as well.
- I want to have fun. - Right.
- Gosh. How is my house? - This place is so nice.
I love this the most.
- The multi-cable? - I can see how you live.
- This is great. - Don't you use this? The 3m cable.
I didn't know there was a cable that was 3m long.
- You can find them. - This is great.
This completely changes the quality of life.
- It changes the quality of life? - Completely.
This one is 3m, and the one in the bedroom is also 3m.
My voice sounds bad as I had a sore throat that day.
- Let's say I was watching TV. - Right.
- Watching TV like this. - Watching TV and using your phone.
While watching TV, I can turn and place my phone here.
- Right. - Like this.
- And I fall asleep like this. - Gosh.
- That's true happiness. - Right.
Hey, you seem to be using that.
- That? I use it once in a while. - Right.
Show me.
- Hold on. - Do you really use it?
Well, I do,
but this is what's funny about it.
- There are different versions. - Right.
- The warm-up. - Right.
Look at him. He didn't use the pedals.
He won't use them at all.
(Let's see.)
This is what I do. Since the pedal comes off,
- I avoid using it like this. - Try using the pedal.
Try using the pedal.
(He places his feet on the pedals as Hyun Moo tells him to.)
- He didn't know about it. - I didn't know about it.
What?
What happened?
Moomoo's After-Sales Service!
What?
(Smiling brightly)
- What? - I changed the pedal.
- Really? - It's different now, isn't it?
- What? - I changed it.
How did you do that?
What do you mean? I said I was going to fix it.
- Gosh. - After the bazaar,
I felt bad about it.
You felt great, didn't you?
- He looked delighted. - I felt great.
Instead of fixing it in front of him,
it feels better as a pleasant surprise.
- Gosh. He's mischievous. - He always...
- Right. - The mischievous one.
I went around so much to look for the part.
You found this?
- I did. - Hold on.
I didn't know it was supposed to feel that comfortable.
It felt much easier.
Use it freely now.
- Gosh! This is amazing. - It's perfect now.
- What about the previous one? - It's right here.
- It's that one? - I got rid of it.
This one is new.
(He hands him a new part as a spare as well.)
- As a spare part? - Right.
- Change it when you need to. - Nice.
- That was nice of him. - Right.
- The left one would've been used. - Right.
He would have to come again if the left pedal broke.
- I'll place the mat for you. - Even a mat?
Right. Just in case.
- Gosh, this is perfect. - Right.
The machine won't make any noise for the house downstairs,
but this is just to be safe.
The machine barely makes any noise.
It's quiet.
These will be put together.
(He adjusts the pieces together.)
I thought this would be nice to place underneath.
(He gets everything done until the end.)
(Both pedals are working fine now.)
(Moomoo's After-Sales Service was perfect.)
I should buy things at the bazaar next time.
- Mine? - Not yours.
Since the after-sales service is really nice.
Right. I make sure to provide the perfect after-sales service.
- You should check the bedroom. - The bedroom?
This is the hot water mat you gave me.
After the pedal incident,
he felt so bad about it...
and sent me a hot water mat.
- Really? - Yes.
- The hot water mat. - You've been using it.
- It's nice, isn't it? - It's great.
I bought it without getting any discounts.
(He gets on the bed while showing the hot water mat.)
- Gosh! - It's nice, isn't it?
This feels great!
Gosh, I feel much better!
- Gosh. - At first...
(Woo Il turns toward the wall.)
(He slowly raises his arm.)
- What are you doing? - What are you doing?
(They share the warmth through their bodies instead.)
(It's cold in the winter, isn't it?)
(The day he lay with Ju Seung in one bed)
(It's been a while to be in bed with someone.)
(You know what I'm talking about, don't you?)
Look at Ju Seung keeping his eyes closed.
(When he got closer...)
- He's loving it. - He's disgusted.
Gosh.
(It's you today.)
I got goosebumps.
(His arm slowly goes around that man.)
(Shocked)
Gosh, that felt disgusting.
Just like with Sung Hwan,
- you're a killer. - Right.
(The two men enjoyed playing with water last summer.)
(A trembling touch)
(Shaking)
(Killer Moo only goes after the Rainbow Club members.)
I suddenly felt the scent of a man. Gosh.
In case you didn't eat,
- I brought something for you. - What did you bring?
I got up at 7am to make this.
You made it yourself?
What's the hottest thing these days?
Malatang?
Don't talk about something from eight years ago.
Tanghulu?
That was from 15 years ago.
What is something that is hard to get these days?
Oh, the DCK!
- The DCC, not the DCK. - Right. The DCC.
(You made the Dubai chewy cookie?)
Gosh.
- I've tried the DCC three times. - Right.
You really brought the DCC?
I've tried it once.
It's brown.
(Try the one I made.)
(The MCC appears.)
The MCC.
- What is this? - What do you mean?
Isn't this a sirutteok that is rolled into a ball?
How can you call it a sirutteok?
It looks like a sirutteok rolled into a ball.
It's chewy just like a sirutteok.
- The MCC. - The MCC?
I drew that as well.
(The MCC gets handed to him.)
Give it a try first. Give it a try and see how it is.
(He takes a big bite.)
I think it'll be really good.
(Chewing)
How is it?
(Crunchy)
It looks good.
It tastes good.
- It's good, isn't it? - It tastes good.
Right.
But the things inside are too big.
They're supposed to feel like powder inside.
(Embarrassed)
But they feel a bit too big.
It tastes good, though.
It's impossible to get...
- the noodle-like thing these days. - Right.
I made the noodles myself.
They became too thick like kalguksu noodles.
- That's why they feel that way. - I see. They feel this way...
- because they're too thick. - They feel too hard.
The kadayif was the fly in the ointment.
- That was the crucial part. - Right.
If I had bought the kadayif,
- it would've had that texture. - it would've felt the same.
- It's really hard to make. - It's really hard to make.
Right.
It's good, isn't it?
(The MCC has a different texture as it's handmade.)
- It's good. - It has so much pistachios in it.
It's good for you.
It's good when heated in the microwave.
I saw this somewhere.
- Really? - I heard it was good...
when heated in the microwave for ten seconds.
I didn't know that.
The reason for that is to make it gooey.
As it was already made to be gooey,
- it would've been good as is. - Right.
It was already gooey.
- It was already made that way? - Right.
- It makes it gooier. - So the thick ones...
- are heated up. - Right.
- It makes it smoother. - I see.
(The MCC was heated up.)
You heated it up with the plastic bag?
Yes. What's wrong with that?
It will stick to the plastic bag.
I don't think that's the problem.
Right.
- Gosh! - Gosh!
(Shocked)
Why is it like this?
- Gosh. - I heated it up for ten seconds.
You turned it into a big mess.
Why turn it into a big mess...
when I went through all that to make it for you?
I'm not lying. I just heated it up for ten seconds.
It was because you heated it up with the plastic bag.
(A disastrous sight)
Just pick it up and eat from the bag.
There you go.
(Stretching out)
(Disgusted)
Look at Hyun Moo's face!
There you go.
The marshmallow stretches out a lot more now.
- It tastes good, though. - Right. It tastes good.
I'm enjoying what you made like that.
Why would you look at me like that?
Heating it up for ten seconds doesn't seem like a good idea.
- It's just right. - It's just right, isn't it?
- Yes. - If it's too sweet...
The one I tried...
- was way too sweet. - Right.
I wondered why people enjoyed eating something so sweet.
That was the first impression I got from it.
- But this is just right. - Right.
(He takes another bite as it suits his taste.)
Gosh.
Why do you look so appalled?
Why are you looking at me like that?
He was tearing at it from the plastic bag.
But you didn't have to look at me like that.
I didn't realize my face was like that.
I was just eating it.
(Woo Il is really enjoying it.)
Right.
I've just been to Thailand recently.
You got me the hot water mat before I left.
- So out of gratitude... - What did you get me?
I got something hot.
- You're not a big spender. - I'm curious.
- Right. Well, - Why bother?
- it's not the price that matters. - Right.
I got something hot for you.
Is it food?
What is that?
What could that be?
(Looking heavy)
What did you get me?
(Curious)
You love spicy food, don't you?
That's why I brought Thailand's ramyeon.
(Thailand's ramyeon)
It's different from regular ramyeon.
- I love it. - Thailand's ramyeon.
This is the ramyeon sold in Thailand's local stores.
- I love it. - The spicy ramyeon.
It's the tom yum ramyeon.
- The tom yum ramyeon tastes great! - I bought different kinds of them.
The Gen MZers...
- It's a trend? - enjoy them the most.
- I'm curious about how it tastes. - Same here.
And there's this.
Since you love spicy food, I got you a spicy sauce.
(Spicy sauce)
- The spicy sauce. - That was the real deal.
That sauce is great.
I'm not exactly sure about the details of it,
but I asked for the spiciest powder at the store.
- You really bought this for me? - Yes.
I knew you loved spicy food.
- I love spicy food. - Right.
You must've tried all kinds of spicy food in Korea.
- That was why I went all Thai. - The spicy taste of Korea...
- isn't enough for me. - Right.
- It was the perfect gift. - Right.
- He loves spicy food. - I collect spicy sauces.
He loves spicy food and ramyeon.
Gosh, that's perfect.
Of course, including the money spent on everything,
it's a hassle to pack everything into the suitcase.
Right.
It was really touching that he went through all that for me.
It's a hassle to buy gifts abroad.
It uses up so much space.
- It's a hassle to buy gifts. - Right.
Thank you so much. It was the perfect gift for me.
Should we try cooking one packet of ramyeon?
(He heads to the kitchen to cook the ramyeon.)
- Just to give it a taste. - Right.
- Do you not have a proper meal? - Sorry?
Do you not have a proper meal at night?
(Hyun Moo gets some time to rest thanks to him.)
I want to stay the night here.
(He even falls asleep.)
- He must've felt tired. - Right.
(The owner of the house cooks the noodles in the meanwhile.)
(He mixes the sauce diligently.)
- Is it a bibim ramyeon? - It feels a bit like that.
I think it looks a bit bland.
Hold on.
I should've gotten rid of more of the water.
That was why I added more of that powder.
- It looks appetizing. - Thai noodles are the best.
(Shall I try the spiciness of Thailand?)
Just to give it a taste.
How is it?
- Is it okay? - It's good.
(I'll also try a bite.)
It's good.
(He slurps it down wildly.)
- What does it taste like? - I wonder.
I'm so curious.
- There's the Buldak Ramyeon. - Right.
It's a bit like that with a slight taste of Thailand.
Right.
(The noodles are slurped without any leftovers.)
It will taste great with some cilantro.
- Right. That would be perfect. - Right.
- Gosh, that was great. - It tastes good.
It's good.
I finished it in two bites.
(He picks up the ramyeon packets right away.)
I'll give you a plastic bag.
(This is all for Moomoo.)
That was great.
(Shaking)
- Here. - Gosh, Thai vibes.
They're packed like this in the markets of Thailand.
In the plastic bag.
(He has a lot of things to carry just like when he first came.)
- That was a great meal. - Great.
I'll make sure to enjoy them. Thank you.
I'm getting more from you.
- Get back safely. I'll use it well. - I'll...
- I'll come for a sleepover. - Right.
- Use it well. - Okay.
- I'll get going now. - Bye!
- Bye! - Bye!
- It's a heartwarming sight. - Right.
I didn't even turn back as I had many other places to visit.
- This was the first house. - Right.
(Current time: 4:30pm)
It's already 4:30pm?
- It's already 4:30pm? - It was raining as well.
- There was so much traffic. - It's raining as well.
(He heads to the next house while listening to music.)
I love this song.
(The crowded and noisy world)
(He sings his heart out.)
(Singing his heart out)
I think I'm almost there.
Who is the second guest of Moomoo's After-Sales Service?
It's a completely different house...
from the house you just saw.
Gosh.
(Hyun Moo has arrived somewhere.)
- Gosh. - Gosh.
It's a completely new building.
- Where could this be? - It's a new building.
- It looks really nice. - Who could it be?
(Take my prank.)
(Opening)
The crowded and noisy world
(Have you been doing well, Hue?)
- It's Hue. - Right.
(Was silent except our beating hearts)
You're the first person to come into my house like this.
(Touched)
- Right. - As it was raining,
I came while listening to "The Rainy Day We Met."
Really?
("The Rainy Day We Met" from "Maybe Happy Ending")
(He sang his heart out with Hue's musical number...)
(on the way there.)
- It was this song. - I didn't know it was that.
It was this song.
No one realized it was that song.
Even after so many hints.
Your house is really nice.
It's the interior design I love the most.
(A house with great vibes with Hue's touch)
It's neat.
I want to live like that.
Show me around the house first.
- The house? - Right.
(Very excited)
- Here. - The bedroom?
- It's my study. - May I take a look?
- Your study? - My workroom.
- Your workroom? - This is it.
What is this smell? It smells really nice.
- I love using air fresheners. - Gosh.
There's not a speck of dust in the house.
Not a single speck.
You will be able to feel the dust if you touch things.
Gosh! It's great.
(Startled)
Right.
- Right. - What is it?
(A piano placed in the corner of Hue's study)
From the bazaar.
- Gosh, he's actually using it. - I'm proud of it.
Are you using it well?
Actually, I haven't been able to connect the power.
- What? Why? - Why didn't he use it?
It's been hectic for me,
traveling back and forth between Seoul and New York.
- Oh, really? - Yes.
You didn't connect it at all. You've been busy, that's why.
(Last time, at the bazaar, )
(he met the keyboard like fate.)
(This is nice.)
(It's natural to be nice because it's new.)
(I'll write a new musical with this.)
- That's right. - I'll write a new one.
(A Tony Award winner will write a new musical with my keyboard?)
(Come and listen to it when it's complete.)
(Is this real? Or am I dreaming?)
- He fell in love. - My heart fluttered...
after a long time.
That's when I was really moved by Writer Hue Park.
So I paid a visit to see if he was using the keyboard well.
I heard from CODE KUNST...
that a pedal makes all the difference on a piano.
Hyun Moo kept asking me that.
It wasn't an after-service. It was more like giving a free gift.
Hoping he'd write a nice piece,
I went to see him to give him a new pedal.
You didn't connect it at all.
- You've been busy, that's why. - Yes, I...
Gosh, how's your house so clean?
I mean...
(Smiling)
This is crazy. I love it.
- His house is really nice. - I mean...
- I try to keep it neat. - Your place is better than mine.
Out of all the houses...
that were shown on the show,
it's 1 of the top 2 houses that I admire the most.
From its smell to how neat it is.
He doesn't even have much stuff.
It's the ideal house I dream of.
I spend a lot of money and decorate the house...
in a messy way without taste.
I waste money on it.
What I hear from others the most...
is, "That brand produces such products too?"
It's humiliating. That means I wasted money.
- I'm the opposite of Hue. - It's true.
You can't buy good taste with money.
- You seem really moved. - I loved it.
I need to keep it really neat to be able to focus well.
If it's messy, it's a bit...
You don't like cleaning other people's houses, do you?
I don't like it.
You wanted me to go to your place, right?
(Hue, you're quick to catch on.)
- How much will you pay me? - What?
- How much will you pay me? - I'll give you a lot.
I just need it to be in this vibe.
Actually, people around me ask me to decorate their houses.
Yes, his taste is really...
You give off...
a classy old-money style.
- But I'm a minimalist. - No, this is...
what you'd call old-money style.
This is truly rich.
(Restless as he's desperate)
Gosh, it's so neat.
Wait. That bag from Trader Joe's.
(Hyun Moo found something.)
- You have that? - Actually...
It's hip too.
Do you know?
Right. It's hard to get that bag these days.
It's the tote bag you have to stand in line for.
- For a tote bag? - You have to line up at opening.
It's hip too.
- Well, I got this... - It's pretty.
While I was in LA...
to give it to you.
(Oh, my)
- Look at him. - That's a bit too much.
- I love things like that. - You didn't have to go that far.
- You're right. It's so popular. - It's crazy.
- It's DCC. DCC of bags. - Yes, it is DCC of bags.
(Feeling hurt)
- It's different from Thai ramyeon. - I mean...
(My goodness)
- As for Thai ramyeon... - You cried over a shopping bag.
As for the ramyeon, I was like, "Oh, you have this too."
But he bought the bag for me.
I also bought the ramyeon for you too.
(I know.)
You're sensitive to trends.
- It's hard to get this. - You're TSM.
Try holding it.
It suits your current outfit.
- It's perfect. - It does suit him.
Pistachio?
- Gosh. - Try carrying it.
- Do I look like a New Yorker? - The size is perfect too.
It's perfect. I really wanted this.
You should put MCC in it and sell them at people's homes.
I'm glad.
Actually, it doesn't cost much.
- It's really cheap. - It's not a matter of price.
- It's hard to get it. - You're right.
I put a special gift for you in the bag.
- Really? - Yes.
Oh, my!
- What is it? - Something's in it.
I went to the Grammy Awards.
- What kind of cap is it? - He's the best.
It's a limited edition.
That's so cool.
Gosh, he's thriving.
(I'm proud of you.)
I hate them so much.
- Why? - Why didn't you win the award?
Why not give the award to you? I saw it.
The Grammy Awards was a really nice event...
even if I didn't win an award.
- That's right. - Of course.
So many excellent singers...
put on amazing performances,
so I soon forgot that I didn't win an award.
I really enjoyed it excitedly.
I'd never be able to get this.
- A true musician. World-class. - That's really cool.
Of course it is. It's impossible to get it.
- It's impossible for Hyun Moo. - What is this?
It's a Grammy Awards T-shirt.
- How did you know I like these? - The emblem is cute.
I just thought you'd like things like this.
- He's staring intently. - You can only get these there.
Oh, my.
(Shocked)
- What is it? - I love it. How crazy. It's so hip.
- It's a pistachio look. - A badge.
- A badge? - A badge.
- You really can't get that. - You really can't.
(Sulky)
This is really special.
- On the day of the award, - How many gifts did he get?
They gave out chocolate in case we got hungry.
But I just brought it back.
I still haven't had it.
- It's better if you don't. - It's pretty.
It's so pretty. I'm about to die.
It's driving me crazy. I love things like these.
I'm about to get upset.
The ramyeon is expensive too. It's from another country.
Of course. I'm eating it well. I had three already.
I'm eating it while thinking about you.
I got such good gifts from you.
Not at all.
Gosh, I'll keep them well.
You gave me a nice keyboard, so you deserve them.
- Actually, I... - Yes?
What? Is someone here?
It must be my food.
You ordered something?
- He ordered food. - You're eating again?
- I haven't eaten yet, so... - You haven't?
It's late lunch, but...
I came at the right timing.
I ordered some sushi.
He ordered food that doesn't smell.
I wonder how his house smells.
- It's not too much. It's subtle. - The scent is all over?
Like an automatic diffuser. You know what it is, right?
- I know. - Like the ones in bathrooms.
- How... - What about Woo Il's place?
It smelled like my parents' place.
It was nice too. The warm smell of a parents' place.
Woo Il is upset.
Next time you come to my place, I'll put the diffuser...
on your philtrum as soon as you enter.
- I'll apply it myself before going. - It'll smell nice all day.
(I'll serve you properly next time.)
- I ordered a lot. - You did?
I think you can eat with me.
Sure. You should hurry up and eat.
Gosh, things like this too. It's beautifully placed.
Where did you get a plate like this?
It's a dish I really like.
Gosh, how do I develop tastes like this?
- Even the lamp is hip. - It's so nice.
- I know. - Your house is so hip.
(Impressed)
Hyun Moo, there are different kinds.
Eat whichever piece you want.
(He plated the sushi nicely too.)
- He plated them nicely. - He even plated them for me.
(Taking a sip of water first)
(Taking a glance)
Where's that cup from?
Actually, it's five dollars each.
- It looks expensive for no reason. - It's not expensive.
It was around 5 or 8 dollars.
It's not expensive.
This one's expensive, right?
This one? It was only a few tens of dollars.
I couldn't find a vase like this. I recently got one.
Right.
This one's a few dollars too.
- Where did you get it? - From Today House.
None of the things I use is expensive.
How come my things are expensive but not pretty?
What's wrong with my taste?
(Feeling bitter for no reason)
(Shall I try the sushi now?)
I was hungry.
(Exclaiming)
You got them from a nice sashimi place.
- Really? It's good to hear. - Yes.
- Even the sashimi was nice. - It's good.
- Come on! - Come on!
- Did you dip it in a diffuser? - You're too much.
Did you dip it in a diffuser or what?
It's not even by the seaside.
It doesn't feel like sashimi by the seaside.
It was more like fine dining.
He only got complimented for the charging cable.
"The 3m cable is nice."
(The only thing that caught Hyun Moo's eye, 3m cable)
What would you have done if it wasn't for the 3m charging cable?
(Goodness)
- I should've bought it for you. - Don't worry.
(He's having another piece.)
(Taking a glance)
(Hesitating)
- You didn't get to eat? - No.
(Staring)
(Hue dips it in soy sauce.)
You didn't have breakfast?
Just a bit.
I did some work that required some thinking.
(He eats it straight without dipping in the soy sauce.)
(Taking a peek)
- Why? Do you feel uncomfortable? - What's wrong?
I got nervous.
I paid so much attention when I ate at Hue's place...
- in case I dropped something. - Oh, in case you dropped something.
He poured soy sauce for me, but I didn't dip it once.
I didn't want to drop soy sauce on his white table,
so I didn't dip it and ate it bland.
That's how much attention I paid.
I felt uncomfortable, actually.
But for Woo Il's place, even if I spill the whole soy sauce,
I feel like I can just wipe it with a rag.
That's how his house is.
(Woo Il's place felt comfortable as though it was his.)
You fall asleep easily there.
Soon, there could be a new production...
- with the piece you write, then. - Well, but...
You don't really watch out for things like that, but you do there.
That's how neat his house was.
Remember how you came into my house with your shoes on?
Your place's interior design was like that of an American home.
What American home? It was an apartment!
There are certain charms...
- that comfortable homes give. - That's right.
My house is comfortable too.
I think I'd feel uncomfortable if Hue told me to live there.
- I can't do things freely. - That's right.
Then if you had a choice, you'd live at mine?
Of course.
I'll make a mess.
Today,
I made something...
to give to you.
What? What did you make?
What's the most popular food in Korea...
- these days? - DCQ.
- DCC. - Oh, he knows.
Correct.
You made it yourself?
I did.
- You made it yourself? - Yes.
I tried it for the first time the day before yesterday.
From where?
I went to Busan...
for a show there.
Actress Park Jin Joo ordered it for me.
- Jin Joo did? - Yes.
I can't wait to try it.
(About to open Moo chewy cookies)
Moo chewy cookies.
I have my own artistic world.
I can't help but reflect on myself. The creative...
The creative energy...
I wonder if I'm releasing enough of it. I'm reflecting on myself.
It sparks such urges, right?
"It sparks such urges, right?"
Also, I wrapped it in a hip style.
(Rustling)
The plastic bag is a bit... Wait, Hyun Moo.
Isn't it hip?
It really doesn't suit that house.
Hey, this is what you call hip.
Wrapping it roughly.
When you took it out...
When you walk your dog...
- Goodness. - Everyone thinks the same.
- And the color had to be this. - Right.
And the bag had to be that.
But... Even if it looks bad,
once you eat it... I made these since 7am.
Don't think it like that.
(Dropped)
It was heavy.
- No, that's a prejudice. - I mean...
Hurry up and get that bag away.
Okay. It's gone.
Its stickiness is...
(Moo chewy cookie's first impression is strong.)
- But... - Yes.
It tastes and smells completely different.
You'll be surprised once you smell it.
(Sniffing)
- The chocolate smell is rich. - I added cocoa.
I used high-quality pistachios.
- Gosh, it's really... - Gosh, the sound.
It's not even sand. It's like glass.
I added a thick layer of kadayif.
How come it's so thick?
- It's like pebbles. - I'll try it.
(Crunch)
(Nervous)
(Exclaiming)
It's good.
It's better than the one I had in Busan.
(Amazed)
- It's better than the real one. - It suits my taste way better.
It's really good.
Writer Hue.
If the fillings were hard...
- That hit his taste exactly. - That's right.
I know.
The New Yorker approved of it.
(He likes the thick kadayif better.)
- This... - It's really good.
It's really hard to make them thin.
I had to squeeze it really hard.
The wetness had to be just right.
The cloth needs to have small holes too.
And you have to be skilled too.
Can you give about three more?
- You see? - Gosh.
You know he really liked it that he asked for more.
That's praise.
If he wants more, that means he really likes it.
It's really good.
I feel so proud.
Hue is the type of person who's straightforward.
And he must be more cool-headed toward cookies...
since he lives in the US too.
That's a prejudice.
I'm so strongly deferential to foreign countries.
Besides saying it was good,
he asked if I had more.
That means...
the domestic market is too small for me.
If I have time,
I'll open a pop-up store...
in front of a theater in New York.
They'll love it so much.
- They'll wait in line for sure. - I can name it K-cookie.
Do you like matcha too?
Of course.
I love matcha.
Hyun Moo, this...
Isn't this the bottom?
I found that out for the first time.
I see!
I think the sticker should be here.
Oh, this is the top.
Yes, since this is the top...
It was my first time using it.
It's more hip that way.
This is the cover.
You're right.
- This is the top. - I thought something was off.
This is modern art too.
- Is that so? - Modern art?
- Right? - Because of the picture...
You can have that later.
(Ta-da!)
(Moomoo's after-service for Hue)
You bought a pedal from Yamaha?
- Because the keyboard is Yamaha's. - Why?
- Why? - Even musicians...
buy the cheapest pedal.
- I shouldn't have bought that. - Because...
(Joking)
- That'd make him happy. - Since you were getting it anyway.
- The authentic one. - Right.
I showed him the logo on the box on purpose.
To emphasize that it's authentic.
- You got the authentic one. - Of course.
- He recognized it. - He did.
- "You got the authentic one." - It was money well spent.
Let me try attaching it.
Hyun Moo, you're like Santa.
It made me really happy to go around giving out gifts.
- You will? - Yes.
- Shall I attach it? - Yes.
(Let's quickly attach it.)
I haven't been able to play it at all,
so I was quite sad.
It's as good as new.
- The after-service is amazing. - Gosh.
I love it.
Can you play any piece?
You need to make a masterpiece on that.
I only played the piano when I was young,
so I started taking a piano lesson again after 30 years.
He's learning to play the piano again.
- Whose piece will you play? - It's by Bach.
- Bach. - Bach.
Now, the piano is being used.
(Amazed)
It met its rightful owner.
(In a trance)
It's like "Whiplash."
(Dipping in his sentimentality instead of soy sauce)
(Yes, this is what I wanted.)
(This is it!)
(Dumbfounded)
(I can't believe my piano is being used like this!)
It met the right owner.
That's classy.
Yes, Hue.
What time is your flight tomorrow?
It's an evening flight.
So I need to start...
- Take your time packing. - packing.
I couldn't pack properly.
Gosh, my precious bag. Thank you.
- Sure. - Hey.
It fits your outfit perfectly.
Later, when you come back from the US,
- let's grab a meal. - Sure.
But I feel like...
(Seriously, Hyun Moo...)
- You didn't say that to me. - You should come too.
- You should come too. - What?
When can you not make it?
Hyun Moo, you'll be punished by the skies for this.
(Joking)
- I mean, - I'm hurt.
I wanted to avoid making plans on those days.
Have a safe trip.
(After promising a meal with Hue)
- Bye. - Bye.
It's really heartwarming.
(To the next after-service place)
It's already night?
Gosh, it's 6:30pm already.
- I was so tired. - You're so diligent.
- It's been almost 12 hours. - That's right.
The traffic was really bad.
It's far.
I'm giving an after-service the whole day.
(Exhausted)
(Driving through the heavy traffic during rush hour)
I'm finally in Seongsu-dong.
Gosh, it took so long.
(Seongdong Bridge, Wansimni-ro)
(He has arrived at the third place for an after-service.)
Call.
- Hello? - Jae Hyeon.
Hyun Moo.
It's Moomoo's after-service.
(The third guest is Jae Hyeon.)
Open the door for me.
(Clicking his tongue)
What was that just now?
- I did this. - His greeting.
He must've been watching me through the screen.
The screen doesn't come on for that.
- Right. The screen doesn't come on. - He did it all by himself.
- The screen doesn't come on. - What was I doing?
The guard must've been shocked.
(Entering the parking lot without realizing it)
(Opening)
(A huge oven fills the entire trunk.)
- Unloading it must be hard. - My goodness.
- It's huge. - Goodness.
(Struggling)
Hyun Moo.
(The third guest appears with a bright smile.)
The third place for Moomoo's after-service is...
Jae Hyeon's, the one I got the oven for.
(Hyun Moo's oven was a troublesome item at the bazaar.)
(He even baked bungeoppang to promote it.)
(It's so good, right?)
(But nobody wanted to buy it.)
(Jae Hyeon was the only one who showed interest.)
(The original price was around 3,500 to 4,000 dollars.)
(I'll give it to you at 1,000 dollars.)
(I'm in!)
(He gladly bought it for his friends who are preparing to open a cafe.)
It was the most expensive item at the bazaar.
- Right. - That's right.
Let me give you a hand.
(The oven finally found its rightful owner.)
It finally found its owner.
- Be careful. - Let's put it down here.
(Careful)
- One, two, three. We got it. - Gosh!
- Are all these needed? - They're all yours.
- Really? - Yes, they're all for you.
These are the stones.
- You need these. - What are they for?
When you bake something.
I think the rack at the bottom is a really good one.
- He made it. - I made it.
- Really? - Yes.
We finally have someone who recognizes that.
- After it's sold. - I know.
So people know its value.
(Feeling proud)
- Shall we just move like this? - Yes, let's just go.
It has wheels.
Of course.
(Smoothly moving to the elevator thanks to the wheels)
Hold on.
(Pressing)
I'll leave the doors open.
No!
- No way! - What is it?
(What's waiting for the two behind the doors...)
(are ten stairs.)
- It doesn't lead to the elevator. - No, it doesn't.
- We needed to climb that. - Of course.
No, it's okay.
- Are you serious? - I'm serious.
I thought of taking it back home...
and hiring someone.
It's unbearably heavy.
(He struggled to move it even at his place.)
- Are you serious? - I'm serious.
(You want me to climb the stairs?)
(Next story)
(In front of Seoul Station at 5am in the morning)
(CODE KUNST is eagerly waiting for someone.)
There he is.
(Hey.)
(Actor Lee Dong Hwi)
Hey.
(Seoul Station TPO of a fashionista?)
(The place they headed to from the crack of dawn)
(Busan Station)
(Filled with block toys that he likes)
(Visiting a special vintage shop)
(It opens at 2pm.)
(At 2pm?)
If it opens at 2pm...
(They miscalculated the time big time.)
(They go shop at vintage shops for now.)
(They begin searching for treasure.)
(This is mine.)
(But I...)
(My clothes...)
(are the most vintage here.)
(Moved by Dong Hwi's taste)
(They found a destination that wasn't part of their plan.)
(It's CODE KUNST.)
(Cat population gap, filled, empty)
Sung Woo, you're popular.
(You're popular.)
(Laughing)
(Still, they're so cute.)
(Is it okay to be this happy?)
(The luck given...)
(to those who didn't plan ahead)
(There's a block toy shop around here?)
(Doubtful)
(Dong Hwi, trust me.)
(The place that's crazy obsessed with blocks)
(Incredible history)
(Incredible scale)
(A series of precious block toys)
(It's a shark!)
(It's a crocodile!)
(It's a glow-in-the-dark ghost.)
(Is he spending 10,000 dollars today?)
(Dong Hwi, it's a monkey!)
(It's a monkey!)
(They have a banana too.)
(I heard you.)
Dong Hwi.
(A Build-It-Yourself Day)
(No!)
(They're left with...)
(the oven and stairs.)
(President Moo's after-service continues.)
Keep going!
(I feel anxious.)
(Don't go!)
(Screaming)
(Can you make it to my place?)
(Another obstacle met at his house)
(After-service stuck at the entrance)
(It's getting more and more chaotic.)
(But the after-service can't stop here.)
(The owner of the house seems somewhat uneasy.)
(If you don't want it, I won't do it.)
(No, I... I want it.)
(A battle of egos for the after-service?)
(If you want it, let's give it a try.)
(No.)
(Will Moomoo's after-service fail just like this?)
(I'll end this with my secret weapon, Moo chewy cookies.)
(I had to line up for 4 hours.)
(Highly expectant)
(Can I open my eyes now?)
(Hyun Moo, this really is an after-service, right?)
(Shocked)
(Choked up)
(Moomoo's Chaotic After-Service)